Guide to the University Photography records, [ca.1989-2001]
University Photography records,
- Faculty and staff
  - I-K
    - Jouhavel, Christian, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Kabcenell, Andrea, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Kabelack, Linda, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Kaczinski, David, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Kady, Rebecca, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Kahn, Alfred, 1969-1993 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Kahn, Lawrence, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Kahn, Peter, 1969-1984 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Kalb, Bernard, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Kallfelz, Fran, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Kalos, Marvin, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Kammen, Michael, 1971-2001 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      Negatives and a press release included
    - Kamp, Marie, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Kan, Edwin, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Kanapan, Srikanta, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Kanbur, Ravi, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Kaplan, David, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Kaplan, Joann, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Kaplan, Steven, 1984-1996 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Karasick, Paul, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Karp, Peter, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Karplus, Andrew, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Katz, Harry, 1989-1996 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Katz, Norm, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Katz, Steven, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Katzenstein, Peter, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Kawasaki, Guka, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Kay, Robert, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Kayastha, Ved P., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Kazarinoff, Michael, Undated (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Keane, Thomas C., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Keich, Uri, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Keil, Frank, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Keller, Harry, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Kellerwiles, Tracey, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Kelley, Michael, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Kelly, Ed, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Kelly, Henry, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Kelly, Tom, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Kemble, Karen, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Kendall-Casella, Anne, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Kendler, Bernhard, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Kenkel, Don, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Kennedy, Joe, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Kennedy, Kenneth, 1978-2001 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Kennedy, Laing, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Kennet, Todd, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Kenney, Anne, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Kenney, Renee, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Kerr-Donovan, Yariela, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Kerschner, Bernie, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Kerwin, James, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Keske, Carl, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Khan, Awal, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Khurana, Beana, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Kidder, Jeff, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Kiefer, Nicholas, 1986-1989 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Kim, Sung Guk, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Kim, Young, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Kimes, Sheryl, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - King, Bente, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - King, Joe, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - King, Paul, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - Kinoshita, Tokhiro, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Kinsland, Cynthia, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - Kinter, Paul, Undated (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - Kinzelberg, Harvey, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - Kiplinger, Austin, 1982-1997 (Box 6, Folder 136)
      Undated negatives included
    - Kira, Alexander, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Kirkland, Earl, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Kirkwood, Gordon, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 139)
      Press release included
    - Kittleman, Margo, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Klein, Richard, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Klein, Tom, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Kleinberg, Jon, 1966, Undated (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - Klen, Linda, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - Klessing, Dan, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Kline, Ronald, 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Klugewicz, Debbra, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Knapp, James, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Knudsen, Ejnar, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - Knuth, Barbara, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Koh, Carolyn, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Kohut, Kim, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Kohut, Robert, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 153)
    - Koll, Rob, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 154)
    - Kollias, George, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 155)
    - Kooperman, David, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 156)
    - Kornegay, Kevin, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - Koslowski, Barbara, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 158)
    - Kotlikoff, Michael, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 159)
    - Kozen, Dexter, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - Kozlowski, Robert, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 161)
    - Kraft, Cheryl, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - Kramer, Tane, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - Kramhansl, James, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 164)
    - Kramnick, Isaac, 1993-2002 (Box 6, Folder 165)
    - Krass, Steve, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 166)
    - Kraus, William, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - Krause, Barbara, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - Kresovich, Steve, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 169)
    - Kress, Steve, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 170)
    - Krikorian, Elaine, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - Kritz, Mary, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 172)
    - Kroch, Carl, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - Kroll, Jules B., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kroma, Margaret, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Krook, Lennart, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Krusius, Peter, 1988-1999 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Kruzansky, Charlie, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kuder, John, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Kuhn, Brenda, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Kuki, Atsuo, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Kuniholm, Peter Ian, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Kunin, Madeline, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Kurasawa, Yoh, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Kusse, Bruce, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Kutty, Nandinee, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Kuzora, John, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Kyle, Molly, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - L-M
    - LaCapra, Dominick, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Lacey, Bill, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - LaFace, Tom, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - LaFeber, Walter, 1970-1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Set of negatives and one photograph undated
    - Lal, Amit, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Lam, Gail, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Lambert, David, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Lambert, Jack, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Lambert, Sarah, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - L'amoreaux, Cheryl, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lance, Richard, 1988-1994 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Land, Bruce, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Landolf, Laura, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Landry, Laurie, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Lang, Barbara, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Langbauer, William, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Lang-Biz, Roger, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Langhans, Robert, 1973-1994 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Lankhamerer, Rob, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Lantz, Barbara, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - LaQuatra, Joseph, 1994-2003 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Item from 2003 is loan form only. Negatives included
    - Lark, Robert, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Larue, Thomas, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Lassoie, Jim, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Last, Rob, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Latham, Michael, 1980-2000 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Latimer, Tomitra, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Lauver, Terry, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Law, Gordon, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Law, Jane Marie, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Law, Nancy, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Lawler, Edward, 1996-2001 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Lawrence, Greg, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Lawrence, John, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Lazor, Bill, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Lazzaro, Claudia, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Lederer, Sally, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Ledford, Richard A., 1994 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Lee, Angela, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      Photocopy and negatives only
    - Lee, Benson, Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Lee, Chang, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Lee, Charles R., 1997 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Lee, David, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Lee, Kelvin, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Lee, Lee C., 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      Two photographs undated. Photocopies included
    - Lee, Lillian, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Lee, Nancy, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Lee, Stephen, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Leggatt, Graham, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Lehmann, Johannes, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Lehr, George, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Lei, Xingen, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Leibouich, Sid, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Lembo, Arthur, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Lengeman, Frederick, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Lentini, Marc, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Leonard, Marge, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Leonard, Sam, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Leopardi, Lisa, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Leopold, Carol, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Lepage, Peter, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Lerch, Linda, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Lesser, Miriam, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Levet, Claude, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Levin, Richard, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Levin, Simon, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Levine, Gilbert, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Levinthal, David, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Levitsky, David, 1993-2003 (Box 7, Folder 84)
      One photograph undated. Negatives and photocopies included
    - Levitt, Bruce, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Lewenstein, Bruce, 1989-2001 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Lewis, David, 1985-1994 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Lewis, Karen, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Lewis, Phillip, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Ley, Doug, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Li, Che-Yu, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Li, Yuying, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Liang, Guyan, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Libby, Robert, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Liboff, Richard, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Lieberman, A., Undated (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Liggett, Jim, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Likens, Gene E., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Linn, Charles, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Linster, Christiane, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Linusson, Elisabeth, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Lipitz, Allison, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Lipsky, David, 1990-1998 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Lipson, Hod, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Lipson, Michal, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Lisk, Donald, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Littauer, Raphael, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 107)
      Description on back of one photograph
    - Little, Jeannette, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Liu, Philip, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Liu, Rui Nai, 1994-2002 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - LiVigne, Tom, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Lo, Jane, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - Lo, Yu-Hwa, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Lobovsky, Emil, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Locey, Jean, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Loew, Franklin, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Loker, Suzanne, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Lomax, Kathy, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Lombard, Mary Beth, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Lombardi, Tarky, Undated (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Lomocano, John, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Long, Cathy, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Longcoy, Valerie, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Loomis, Ron, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Loper, Ruby, Undated (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Lorber, Julie (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Loring, Roger, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Losey, John, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Louge, Michael, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Lowe, Jack, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Lowell, Ed, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Lowi, Ted, 1972-2001 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Loy, Christopher, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Lucas, Carol, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Lucas, Mona, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Lucey, Robert, Undated (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Ludders, John, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Luechtenborg, William, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Lund, Daryl, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Lundberg, Craig, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Luo, Dan, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Lurie, Alison, 1977-1998 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Lust, Barbara, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 143)
      Two sets of negatives undated
    - Lust, Robert, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Luster, Marty, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Lynch, Brian, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Lynch, Tim, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Lynch, Tom, Undated (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Lynn, Mike, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - Lynn, Stuart, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Lynn, Victoria, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Lynn, Walter, 1969-1999 (Box 7, Folder 152)
      One photograph undated. Press release included
    - Lyon-Bestor, Victoria, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Maas, Dan, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Maas, James, 1969-2001 (Box 7, Folder 155)
      Undated photographs and negatives. Press release and some photo descriptions included
    - Maccorkle, Carol, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - MacDonald, Neal, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - MacGuffie, Martha, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - Mackin, Jeanne, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Macko, Vladimir, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - Macleod, James, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - Mafiba, Julie, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Magre, Betsy Taber, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - Mahoney, Darael, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Makepeace, Bill, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - Maloney, Tom, 1992-2000 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Malott, Dean, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - Mangurian, Peter, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Mani, Pertha, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - Manocha, Aruind, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Manohar, Rajit, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - Manor, Dan, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Marache, Russ, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - Maranca, Ellen, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - March, Kathryn, 1989-1996 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - March, Kenna, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - Marcham, Fred, 1978-1991 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Marcus, Phil, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - Marcus, Stanley, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - Markwei, Carol, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Marschner, Stephen, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Marsh, Barnaby, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Marsh, Scott, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Marston, Brenda, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Marti, Pat, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Martin, Ann, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Martin, Biddy, 1992-2003 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Martin, Greg, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Martin, Peter, 1986-1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Martinez, Jose, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Masnick, Amy, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Mason, Hugh, 1997-2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      Items from 1997 photocopies only
    - Mason, Jim, 1992-1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Matayas, Bob, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Mateo, Ron, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Mathios, Alan, 1992-2002 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Matier, Michael, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Mattens, David, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Matteo, Patricia, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Matterazzo, John, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Matteson, Harry, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Matthews, Ann, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Maxwell, Bill, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      Negatives and letter from the National Academy of Engineering included
    - Maxwell, Lorraine, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - May, Bernie, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - May, Kathy, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Maylin, George, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Mayor, James, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - McBride, Murray, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - McCall, Dan, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - McCann, David, 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - McCartney, Elaina, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - McCasland, Margaret, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - McClafferty, Fred, 1993-2003 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - McClane, Ken, 1988-2002 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - McClintock, Charles, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - McClure, Polly Ann, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - McConkey, James, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - McCormick, Jennie, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - McCouch, Susan, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - McCoy, Maureen, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - McCullough, Cate, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - McDaniel, Boyce, 1968-2000 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - McDermott, Tim, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - McDonald, Dan, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - McDonald, Matthew, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - McGee, Romona, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - McGonigal, Jane, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - McGowan, Kevin, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      Negatives and description of one photograph included
    - McGregor, Douglas, 1978-1986 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - McGuire, Mark, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - McGuire, Richard, Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - McGuire, Saundra, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - McGuire, Steve, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - McGuire, William, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - McHugh, Matthew F. (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - McKean, Mike, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - McKee, Sally, Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - McKenna, Kevin, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - McKenna, Zach, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - McMahon, Kate, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - McMinn, William, 1984-1991 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - McNeil, Richard, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - McPhee, Jim, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - McQuade, Tyler, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - McVoy, Catherine, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Meador, Rhonda, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Mebane, Walter, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Medina, Greg, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Medville, Karen, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Mei, Tsu-Lin, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Meier, Richard, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Meilman, Phil, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Meinig, Peter, 1997-2002 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Meinwald, Jerrold, 1974-2000 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Meislahn, Nancy, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Menschel, Ronay, 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Merek, Eileen, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Merrill, W.G., Undated (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Mersereau, Darcie, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Mersi, Sidney, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Merton, Allen, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Merwin, Ian, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Messmer, Pete, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Meyburg, Arnim, 1996-2002 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Michaely, Roni, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Michels, Robert, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Mihashi, Toshitumi, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Miles, Sue, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Milkovich, George, 1988-2000 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      Photocopy, negatives, and an undated negative included
    - Miller, Clark, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Miller, Lee N., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Miller, Matt, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Miller, Paula, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Miller, Phil, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Miller, Robert, 1971-1997 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Miller, William, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Milles, Beth, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Milligan, Robert, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Millman, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Milstein, Howard, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Minch, Bradley, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Miner, Joanne, 1994-1999 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Mingle, James, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Minor, Ron, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Mitchel, Olivia, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Mitchell, Charles, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Mitra, Tapin, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Mitrano, Tracy, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Moen, Phyllis, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 111)
      Two photographs undated. Negatives included
    - Moffat, Ann, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Mohammed, Hussini, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Mohanty, Satya, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Moja, Teboho, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Mondy, Nell, 1996-2000 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Monk, David, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Monroe, Cindy, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Monroe, Jonathan, 1992-2000 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Mont, Daniel, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Montemagno, Carlo, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Moody-Adams, Michelle, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Moon, Francis, 1986-2002 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Moore, Charles, 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Moore, David, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Moore, Dick, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Moore, Lois, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Mooz, Robert, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Morato-Peña, Luis, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Morehouse, Roger, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Morely, Jay, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Morenus, Peter, 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - Morey, Richard, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Morgan, Julia, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Morgan, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - Morgan, Steve, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Morin, James, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Morris, Chris, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Morrison, David, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Morrison, George, 1992-2000 (Box 8, Folder 140)
    - Morrison, Mary, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Morrison, Toni, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Morrisset, Greg, 1998-2001 (Box 8, Folder 143)
    - Morse, John, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 144)
    - Morse, Robert, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    - Morton, Lois, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 146)
    - Mosher, Robert, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 147)
    - Moss, Simeon, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 148)
    - Mt Pleasant, Jane, 1991-2000 (Box 8, Folder 149)
      Photocopy and negatives included
    - Mucha, Peter, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 150)
    - Mueller, Jeanne, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 151)
    - Mukerjee, Subrata, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 152)
    - Muller, Steve, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Mullins, Carol, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - Munger, Henry, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Munkenback, Nancy, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - Murdoch, Scott, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - Murphy, Colleen, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Murphy, Susan, 1985-2002 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Murray, Albert, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Murray, Tim, 1988-2002 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - Murray-Rust, Catherine, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 162)
    - Mutkoshi, Stephen, 1986-1998 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Mutschler, Martha, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Myers, Andrew, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Myers, Fred, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 166)
    - Myers, Linda, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 167)
  - N-P
    - Naidoo, Kevin, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - Nash, Abby, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 169)
    - Nasrallah, Mike and June, 1990-1999 (Box 8, Folder 170)
      Negatives and photocopy only
    - Nathaneilz, Peter N., 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 171)
    - Nation, John, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 172)
    - Neafsey, John, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 173)
    - Neiderlander, Rebecca, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 174)
    - Nelson, Eric, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 175)
    - Nelson, Laurel, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 176)
    - Nelson, Mark, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 177)
    - Nelson, Raquel Ann Lacey, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 178)
    - Nelson, Suzy M., 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 179)
    - Neohein, Malden, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 180)
      Three photographs undated
    - Netravali, Anil, 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 181)
    - New, Maria I., Undated (Box 8, Folder 182)
    - Newton, Mary Ann, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 183)
    - Nicholas, Bert, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 184)
    - Nichols, Benjamin, 1975-1997 (Box 8, Folder 185)
    - Nichols, Carol, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 186)
    - Nicholson, Chuck, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 187)
    - Nicholson, Linda, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 188)
    - Nicholson, Phil, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 189)
    - Nickerson, Rhea, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 190)
    - Niemand, Arno, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 191)
    - Nieporent, Drew, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 192)
    - Nillman, Richard, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 193)
    - Nobel, Angela, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 194)